[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":83848,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":95963,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":34042,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":130005,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2277,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":132282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6221,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":138513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1307,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":139820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":12567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":152388,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1893,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":154283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4752,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":159036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1125,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":160163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum  is 6 or  bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4605,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":164772,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1535,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":166308,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8461,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":174771,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1088,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":175860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4221,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":180084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1110,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":181196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember,  to perf orm +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7862,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":189059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":957,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":190018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3761,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":193780,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":194892,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7786,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":202678,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":891,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":203571,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":41194,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":244771,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Sim ilarly,  3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":441924,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":686697,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":9870,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":696567,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1383,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":697950,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of  an elem ent is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4324,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":702274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":703257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":708063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Corr ect! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1050,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":709113,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":713427,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":932,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":714369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /> <br /> ( Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3654,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":718023,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":7518,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":725541,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, the inverse of 0 is 0, the inverse of 1 is 5 and the inverse of 5 is 1, the inverse of 2 is 4 and the inverse of 4 is 2, and finally the inverse of 3 is 3. Do you see a relationship between an element and its inverse under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"ye s","response_history":["yes"],"rt":67049,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":792590,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":86916,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":879506,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub > 1. Bec ause of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":118166,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":997674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":7207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":1004881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1163,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":1006044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":4171,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":1010215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":48492,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":1058707,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":40285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1098992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1781,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1100783,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5664,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1106457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1329,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1107786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Let's review: under +<sub>6</sub>, 1 and 5 are generators. However, 0, 2, 3, and 4 are not generators. Try playing with these non-generators and seeing which elements each of them does generate (i.e. which elements you can get by combining each non-generator with itself repeatedly). Do you see relationships among particular subsets of the elements that are not generators under +<sub>6</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No ","No. there are no relat","No. there are no rela ","No. t here are no rel","No. there are no re","No. there is no relationship amond the ","No. there is no relationship amond","No. there is no relationship amon","No. there is no relationship amo","No. there is no relationship am","No. there is no relationship among the elements that are not generators","No"],"rt":590370,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1698156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10613,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1708769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1","9","1"],"rt":24021,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1732790,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1012,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1733802,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6192,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1739994,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8273,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1748277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6803,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1755080,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3931,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1759011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1765344,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got  your an swer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I got my answer by adding 4 and 1 and since it is less than 9 it stays the same. the answer is 5","response_history":["I got my answer by adub","I got my answer by adu","I got my answer by adding 4 and 1 and since it is less than 9 it stays the same. the answer is 5"],"rt":50159,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1815503,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The answer is 3. I added 8 and 4. Since 12 is greater than 9 i subtract 9 from 12 which leaves the answer 3","response_history":["The answer is 3. I added 8 and 4. Since 12 is greater than 9 i subtract 9 from 12 which gli","The answer is 3. I added 8 and 4. Since 12 is greater than 9 i subtract 9 from 12 which gl","The answer is 3. I  added 8  and 4. Since 12 is greater than 9 i subtract 9 from 12 which g","The answer is 3. I added 8 and 4. Since 12 is greater than 9 i subtract 9 from 12 which leaves the and","The answer is 3. I added 8 and 4. Since 12 is greater than 9 i subtract 9 from 12 which leaves the answer 3"],"rt":69410,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1884923,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"The identity is 0 because it is the only number when added with 9 gives 9","response_history":["The identitiy ","The identity  ","The identity un ","The identity und ","The identity under  "," ","T ","Th ","The  ","The i ","The id ","The ide ","The iden ","The ident ","The identi ","The identit ","The identity  ","The identity i ","The identity is  ","The identity is 0  ","The identity is 0  b ","Th e identity is 0 be ","The identity is 0 bec ","The identity is 0 beca ","The identity is 0 becau ","The identity is 0 because  ","The identity is 0 because i ","The identity is 0 because it  ","The identity is 0 because it i ","The identity is 0 because it is  ","The identity is 0 because it is t ","The identity is 0 because it is th ","The identity is 0 because it is the  ","The identity is 0 because it is the on ","The identity isl 0 because it is the on ","The identity isly 0 because it is the on ","The identity isly  0 because it is the on ","The identity isly 0 because it is the on ","The identity isl 0 because it is the on ","The identity is 0 because it is the on ","The identity is 0 because it is the only number when addeed","The identity is 0 because it is the only number when addee","The identity is 0 because it is the only number when added with 9 gives 9"],"rt":64344,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1949267,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"The inverse is 4","response_history":["The inverse is 4"],"rt":50805,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":2000072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7","7"],"rt":14399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":2014471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The inverse is 6 because when added to 3 the result is 9","response_history":["The inverse is 6 because when added to 9 the =","The inverse is 6 because when  added t o 9 the ","The inverse is 6 because when added to 9 the","The inverse is 6 because when added to 9 th","The inverse is 6 because when added to 9 t","The inverse is 6 because when added to 9 ","The inverse is 6 because when added to 9","The inverse is 6 because when added to 3 the result is 9"],"rt":39949,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":2054420,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you cannot get the number 7 by adding the number together","response_history":["no because you cannot get the number 7 by adding the number to gether","no because you cannot get the number 7 by adding the number together"],"rt":128189,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":2182609,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a  generat or under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because you cannot get the numbers 1 through 9 by adding the 3's","response_history":["no. ","no.","no because you cannot the","no because you cannot th","no because you cannot t","no because you cannot get the numbers 1 throught ","no because you cannot get the numbers 1 throught","no because you cannot get the numbers 1 through 9 by addub","no because you cannot get the numbers 1 through 9 by addu","no because you cannot get the numbers 1 through 9 by adding the 3;s","no because you cannot get the numbers 1 through 9 by adding the 3;","no because you cannot get the numbers 1 through 9 by adding the 3's"],"rt":102219,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":2284828,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got y our answ er.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no. because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 5's and subtracting 9's for anything higher than 9","response_history":["no. because you cn","no. because you caa","no. because you cannot get th ","no. because you cannot get the u","no. because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 5's and subtracting 9's for ani","no. because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 5's and subtracting 9's for anything higher thna","no. because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 5's and subtracting 9's for anything higher thn","no. because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 5's and subtracting 9's for anything higher than 9"],"rt":130878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":2415706,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for anything over 9","response_history":["no/ because you cannot get te","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 9's and ","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 9's and","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 9'","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 9","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for antything","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for antythin","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for antythi","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for antyth","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for antyt","n o/ becau se you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for anty","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for ant","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for anu","no/ because you cannot get the number 1 through 9 by adding 6's and subtracting 9's for anything over 9"],"rt":83311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":2499017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":16549,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":2515576,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+n_1","response_history":["1+_","1+n_1"],"rt":61011,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2576587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which gives the answer 0","response_history":["x+n_x The formual","x+n_x The formua","x+n_x The formulat","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is w","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which brings ","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which brings","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which bring","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which brin","x+n _x The f ormula for the inverse is the number which bri","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which br","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which b","x+n_x The formula for the inverse is the number which gives the answer 0"],"rt":71327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2647914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"There is no pattern as to which elements are generators","response_history":["I","There is no pattern as to which elements are generators","There is no pattern as to which elements are generator","There is no pattern as to which elements are generato","There is no pattern as to which elements are generat","There is no pattern as to which elements a re gener ators"],"rt":46148,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2694072,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4028,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2698100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3229,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2701329,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":21349,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2722678,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number might end up not being a multiple of n","response_history":["It doesnt ","It doesnt","It doesn't have to be a multople ","It doesn't have to be a multople","It doesn't have to be a multopl","It doesn't have to be a multop","It doesn't have to be a multo","It doesn't have to be a multiple of n ","It doesn't have to be a multiple of n","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a dicisor ","It doesn't h ave to b e a multiple of a dicisor","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a diciso","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a dicis","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a dici","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a dic","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n.","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n becu","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because when ","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because when","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because whe","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because wh","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because w","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is f","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater then","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater the","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than 9","It doesn't have to b e a mult iple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number ","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number ","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number ","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number ","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number might end up not being a multopl","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number might end up not being a multop","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n because if it is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number might end up not being a multo","It doesn't have to be a multiple of a divisor of n becau se if it  is greater than n and n has to be subtracted the number might end up not being a multiple of n"],"rt":165486,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2888164,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Never","response_history":["Sometimes","Never"],"rt":208801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":3096975,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"It will always be the generator for th e number . It never changes.","response_history":["the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. There for ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. There for","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. There fo","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. There f","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. There ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. There","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse is alos","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse is alo","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse is al","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse is ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if i ts inver se is","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse i","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse was also a generator then ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse was als","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if its inverse","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore if","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore i","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore you cannot find the numbers ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. Therefore","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. T","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the se t. The s aem","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The sae","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same number","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same numbe","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same numb","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same num","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same nu","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same n","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The same","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The sam","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The sa","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The s","the generator is what is u sed to g et the other numbers in the set. The inverse ca","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The inverse c","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The inverse ","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The in","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The i","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The of the generator cannot be ise","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The of the generator cannot be is","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The of the generator cannot be i","the generator is what is used to get the other numbers in the set. The of the generator cannot be used to find the other numbers","It will always be the gener","It will always be the gene","It will always be the gen","It will always be the ge","It will always be the g","It will always be the generator for the num ber. It  ner","It will always be the generator for the number. It never cahn","It will always be the generator for the number. It never cah","It will always be the generator for the number. It never ca","It will always be the generator for the number. It never changes."],"rt":394816,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":3491791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":13920,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":3505711,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1226,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":3506937,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"25","response_history":["25"],"rt":2528,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":3509465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2689,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":3512154,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure w hich one  is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"calculus 2","response_history":["calculus 2"],"rt":11145,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":3523309,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3497,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":3526806,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of i t but di dn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":4717,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":3531523,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":3535731,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2432,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":3538163,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":1953,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":3540117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2030,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":3542147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":4713,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":3546860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes","response_history":["yes"],"rt":3974,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":3550834,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"This hit was extremely hard","response_history":["This hit was extreely","This hit was extreel","This hit was extree","This hit was extremely hard"],"rt":9582,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":3560426,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.16-0"}]